

WAN KHAIRI

COMODITY MANAGEMENT ASSOCIATE

- 🖀 Lot 1848 Jln 1 Desa Darul Naim Pasir Tumboh, kota bharu 16150 Kelantan, Malaysia
- khairiyusof@gmail.com
- **** 0179692389

PROFILE -----

Name : Wan Khairi Gender : Male

Date of Birth: 27, August 1985

Age: 31 Years Old

Availibility: After 1 Month

OBJECTIVE ----



Engineering Graduate with leadership training and experience with academic training at the Universiti Teknikal Malaysia Melaka. Proven skills in project management, organization and research with a background in office administration and organization. Able to provide employers with administrative support and professional communication skills.

EXPERIENCE

May 2011 - Now

Celestica(M) Sdn Bhd

Position: comodity management associate

Job Description: • To RFQ and ensure complete quote information for purchase requirement • Understand supply chain process and familiar with manufacture distributors • Receive and analyze supplier quote and maintain a good supplier relationship in expediting respond and negotiation • Set IR for new parts in ERP (New Win, EC change, ROHS conversion) • New vendor code setup with competitive supplier terms established

Dec 2010 - Apr 2011

TEKAD Communications SDN BHD

Position: Technician

Job Description :• Installation internet and telephone cabling at JKR site • Splicing and testing fiber optic cable • Pulling coaxial cable for IP core project

Apr 2010 - Nov 2010

Formula Mutakhir SDN BHD

Position: technician

Job Description :• Installation HSBB for TM site • Splicing and testing fiber optic cable at some of TM site • Network set-up at the Cyberjaya • maintenance of PABX at the YaPeiM

Dec 2006 - Apr 2007

Info-Matic Power SDN BHD

Position: intern student

Job Description: • Installation CCTV at TNB Penang and TNB Shah Alam for 1 week. • Wiring Single Phase & Three Phase Circuit at the new office of info-matic, PDRM for 2 weeks • Maintenance and installation of ups at MOF,HKL, PDRM for the 6 months • Network set-up at the new office of info-matic ,at PDRM, LLM for 1 weeks • Installation of rectifier at Celcom transmitter tower for the 6 months • Documentation of sales and maintenance of product that selling in the info-matic office.

EDUCATION --

Jan 2010 - Oct 2010



Kolej Islam Sains Dan Teknologi(KIST) - ECER Program

Major : Certifacate in fiber optic (Grade : pass)

Jun 2004 - Jun 2009



www.MauKerja.my

